(中央咖啡厅)
摩妮卡,我可以借你的保时捷吗?
Monica? Hey, can I borrow the Porsche?
-好的 -太好了!
-Okay. -AII right!
有什么“不准”的呢?
But what is it not?
不准在车上和我女性朋友玩乐
A pIace to entertain my Iady friends.
-还有什么呢? -不准在车上吃义大利面
-And what eIse is it not? -A pIace to eat spaghetti.
非常好,你为什么会需要开车呢?
Very good. What do you need it for anyway?
超级大乐透奖金已经累积到三亿了
The PowerbaII Iottery is up to 300 miIIion...
-但是这里没有在卖彩券 -所以你要开车到康乃狄克州买?
-...and they don't seII tickets here. -So you're driving up to Connecticut?
对,康乃狄克州,不是西维吉尼亚
Yeah, Connecticut. Not West Virginia.
或许我可以开车载你去 我自己也想买几张彩券
Maybe I'II drive you up there. I'd Iike to buy some tickets myseIf.
钱德现在没有在赚钱 三亿对我们可是会很好用的
Yeah, with ChandIer not getting paid, we couId reaIIy use $300 miIIion.
是的,因为如果我还是在老工作 我们会说“要三亿吗?不用,谢谢”
Yes, because if I was at my oId job, we'd say, ''300 miIIion? No, thank you.''
-你可以帮我买吗? -对啊,我也要
-WiII you get me tickets too? -Yeah, me too.
-当然 -我有个点子
-Sure. -I have an idea.
我们可以各出资五十块 把钱集合起来
Why don't we aII pitch in 50 bucks, we'II pooI our money together...
-然后如果我们中奖,我们就照分 -这主意很棒!
-...and then if we win, we'II spIit it. -That's a great idea!
不用,谢了
No, thanks.
-你不想要中乐透吗? -我当然想
-You don't wanna win the Iottery? -Sure I do.
我还想当国王咧
I aIso want to be king of my own country...
探索第一位飞越大西洋的女飞行员 是怎么了
...and find out what happened to AmeIia Earhart.
-还在想女飞行员吗? -那女人就这样消失了!
-StiII on AmeIia Earhart? -The woman just vanished!
说真的,你真的不要加入吗?
SeriousIy, you don't want in on this?
不要,你们知道 中乐透的机率有多大吗?
No. Do you know what your odds are of winning the Iottery?
比你被闪电打到四十二次的机率还小
I mean, you have a better chance of being struck by Iightning 42 times.
但是我们有六个人 所以我们只需要被打到七次
But there's six of us, so we'd onIy have to get struck 7 times.
我喜欢这种机率!
I Iike those odds!
真的,你们,我不敢相信你们会 愿意花两百块钱在乐透上面
SeriousIy, you guys, I can't beIieve you're gonna spend $250 on the Iottery.
这实在太唬烂了吧?
I mean, that's such a bunch of boo-hockey.
我来问
I'II ask.
“唬烂”?
''Boo-hockey''?
我们认为艾玛已经快要开始说话了
Oh, we think Emma's about to start taIking...
所以在她面前我们会小心用字
...so we're trying to be carefuI about what words we use in front of her.
所以准备好 你们会听到很多的“胡说”…
So get ready to hear a Iot of boo-hockey...
“讨厌”还有“惹人烦”等等
...gosh darn it and brother pucker.
你怎么知道她要开始说话了呢?
How do you know she's gonna start taIking?
当我跟她说话时,我几乎可以感觉到 她听得懂我在说什么
When I taIk to her, I aImost feeI Iike she understands what I'm saying.
有点像乔伊
Kind of Iike Joey.
你说什么?
What's that now?
片名:六人行(第九季)
天啊,瞧瞧这全部的彩券 真是紧张刺激
God, Iook at aII these tickets. It's so exciting.
自从六年级后 我就没有赢过任何东西了
I haven't won anything since sixth grade.
吃派大赛吗?
Pie-eating contest?
因为我很胖,你就以为 那是我唯一能赢的比赛吗??
You assume because I was heavy that's the onIy way I couId win something?
不,我看过你埋在蓝莓派里面的照片
No, I saw a picture of you covered in bIueberries.
-那时候真快乐 -是啊
-That was a good day. -Yeah.
-他们在拖吊你的车! -我停在车库里面
-They're towing your car! -I'm parked in a garage on Morton.
他们正在拖吊一辆车
They're towing a car.
我眼花了
And I am seeing spots.
罗斯,你没有在带艾玛! 瑞秋,你也没有在带艾玛!
Ross, you don't have Emma! RacheI, you don't have Emma!
-艾玛呢?艾玛谁在带呢? -乔伊,别紧张
-Where's Emma? Who has Emma? -Joey, reIax.
我妈两小时前来带走她了 你也在场啊
My mother picked her up two hours ago. You were there.
-有吗? -是的,而且你还跟她说话
-I was? -Yes, and you taIked to her.
-我有吗? -她还带来了砂锅菜来
-I did? -She dropped off a casseroIe.
喔,对啊,那个砂锅女士
Oh, yeah, the casseroIe Iady.
你过来看我们中大奖的吗?
Did you come by to watch us win the big bucks?
制片:马克库尼尔斯
Yeah. And then I figured after you win, we can aII go out to the baIcony...
是啊,然后我想在你们中奖后 我们全部到阳台上…
看有小精灵…
...and see a night rainbow with gremIins dancing on top of it.
制片:丹娜克莱恩
在跳舞的夜间彩虹
别接电话!我来接!
Don't touch the phone! I'II get it!
制片:温蒂诺勒
-You think he washed his hands? -HeIIo?
-你觉得他有洗手吗? -哈?
-嘿,查理,有什么消息? -怎么回事?
-Hey, CharIie, what do you know? -What's going on?
编剧:雪瑞比尔星葛拉罕 艾伦普勒马
ChandIer's supposed to find out if he's getting a job at his agency.
钱德想知道他有没有得到 公司内部的一个工作机会
故事:布莱恩布肯纳 撒巴斯汀琼斯
But out of 1 5 interns, they're onIy hiring three.
但在十五名实习生中 他们只聘请三个人
-Tough odds. -Yeah.
-机率真小 -是啊
还真希望能像你们二十四州…
If onIy it were a sure thing Iike your 24-state Iottery.
导演:盖瑞哈佛森
联合彩券的机率一样高
是啊,瞧瞧谁想通了!
Yeah, Iook who's coming around!
该死,好啦,有更多消息再告诉我
Damn it. AII right, caII me when you know more.
-你有得到吗? -一个名额已经被占了
-Did you get it? -One of the sIots got fiIIed.
-被你吗? -注意我的语气
-By you? -Sense the tone.
-不是,一个叫做奈特的小子 -喔,我讨厌那个人
-No, that kid Nate got it. -Oh, I hate that guy.
我是说,真是的,小子 穿上裤子吧!
I mean, come on, kid, puII up your pants!
还有两个名额不是吗?
WeII, there's two spots Ieft, right?
是啊,我真的好想要,我想要被录取
Yeah. I mean, I want this so much. I wanna get one.
也希望我朋友查理被录取
I want my friend CharIie to get one.
其实我不是很在乎查理
Except I don't care about CharIie.
-嘿,你们好 -嘿!
-Hey, you guys. -Hey!
你们不会相信的 我刚刚去找过我的算命师
You are not gonna beIieve this. I just saw my psychic...
她说我今晚一定会中乐透!
...and she said I was definiteIy gonna win the Iottery tonight!
我想要增加好运…
I thought we couId use some extra Iuck...
所以从餐厅带幸运骨头回来
...so I brought a wishbone home from work.
算命师跟幸运骨头? 拜给别人一点机会吧
A psychic and a wishbone? Guys, give someone eIse a chance.
-好了,谁要来做呢? -我可以吗?
-AII right, who wants to do it? -Can I?
素食者从来就没有机会玩幸运骨头
Vegetarians never get to do the wishbone.
真是不公平,我们只是不吃肉
It's reaIIy not fair. Just because we don't eat the meat...
不代表我们不喜欢玩骨头
...doesn't mean we don't Iike to pIay with the carcasses.
好了,瑞秋呢?
AII right. Rach?
我不想要双手沾满火鸡的味道
I don't want that turkey smeII aII over my hands.
我来,我要把砂锅菜的味道盖过去
I'II do it! It'II get the casseroIe stink off of mine.
-希望我会赢 -嗯,没有关系
-I hope I win. -WeII, it doesn't reaIIy matter.
你们的愿望是一样的
You're both wishing for the same thing.
我不能告诉你我许什么愿 要不然不会实现的
I can't teII you what I'm wishing for, or eIse, you know, it won't come true.
对,但是我们都知道你许什么愿
Right. But we know what you're wishing for.
-我不能说 -我了解
-I can't reaIIy say. -I understand.
但是你许的愿 跟我们想的一样,不是吗?
But you're wishing for what we think, aren't you?
我真的很不喜欢这些问题!
I'm not reaIIy comfortabIe with these questions!
-拜! -赶快做!
-PIease! -Just do it!
好的,一,二,三
Okay. One, two, three.
我赢了!嘿!
I won! Hey!
你们知道吗?我确定 你们的愿望会成真
You know what? I'm sure your wish is gonna come true.
但是,为了以防万一 我们来磨擦这个灯,或许精灵会出现
But, you guys, just in case, maybe a genie wiII come out if we rub this Iamp.
那东西好烫!
That thing gets hot!
罗斯,继续说你的笑话吧
Ross, just keep making your jokes.
如果我们中了 你有什么感受?
How are you gonna feeI if we actuaIIy do win?
-你们不会中的 -我知道机率很小
-You're not gonna win. -I know the odds are against us...
但是总是有人会中,可能就是我们 然后你会觉得如何呢?
...but somebody has to win, and it couId be us. And then how you gonna feeI?
我们会说“大家开直升机去海角玩吧”
We're gonna be Iike, ''Everybody, Iet's take our heIicopters up to the Cape.''
而你只能说喔,我不行…
And you're gonna be aII, Iike, ''Oh, I can't, guys.
我们到那边碰面好了 我先帮我的车子加满油
I'II have to meet you up there. I gotta gas up the Hyundai.''
好了,我听过自己在录音带里的声音 我听起来根本不像那样
Okay, I've heard myseIf on tape, and I sound nothing Iike that.
我可以想像头条新闻是 彩券赢家的朋友…
I can see the headIine now: ''Lottery Winners' Friend...
充满懊悔,吃下自己的手臂
...FiIIed With Regret, Eats Own Arm.''
我为什么要吃自己的手臂?
Why wouId I eat my own arm?
你当然不会,但是报纸是我们的 我们爱怎么写就怎么写
WeII, you wouIdn't, but we own the paper. We can print whatever we want.
你知道吗?我帮你出五十块好了
You know what? I'm gonna throw in 50 bucks for you.
-为什么? -因为我知道你认为…
-Why? -Because I know that you think...
乐透是很唬烂的东西
...that the Iottery is boo-hockey...
但是我们全都聚在一起 看开奖,会很好玩的
...but we're aII here, and we're gonna watch the numbers and have fun.
而你是我哥哥,我希望你能参与
And you're my brother, and I want you to be a part of this.
你不需要这样做的,我可以自己出钱
You don't have to do that. I mean, I'II pay for myseIf.
但是你想要让我跟你们一起同乐 真的是太窝心了
But just the fact that you want me to have fun with you guys, that's so sweet.
过来
Come here.
去开个房间吧
Get a room.
那既然你已经加入了 要是中奖,你要做什么事呢?
So now that you're in, what are you gonna do if we win?
-我不知道,或许投资吧 -对,要冷静
-I don't know. I'II probabIy just invest it. -CaIm down.
正经点,你的梦想呢?投资?
SeriousIy, that's your fantasy? To invest it?
喔,我很抱歉,我是说投资吗? 我的意思是“快乐的全部花光光”
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I say, ''invest it''? I meant, ''Be cooI and piss it aII away.''
我知道了!我们该把全部的钱凑起来 买下尼克队!
I know! We shouId pooI aII our money and buy the Knicks!
我不是很在乎尼克队
I don't reaIIy care about the Knicks.
如果我选你当前锋,你就会了
You wiII when I pick you as starting forward.
你会那样做吗?我从没有被选上!
You wouId do that? I never get picked!
我不确定球队会是正确的选择
I'm not sure a sports team is the way to go.
你不让我买尼克队吗? 我不敢相信你要打碎我的梦想
You won't Iet me buy the Knicks? I can't beIieve you're taking this away.
你说的对,这个梦想 已经有十五秒之久了
You're right, it has been your dream for over 1 5 seconds.
他们还有多久才会公布号码呢?妈咪
How Iong untiI they announce the numbers, Mommy?
这个也让我来 什么“妈咪”啊?
I'II take this one too. ''Mommy''?
喔,我已经习惯叫瑞秋…
Oh, I've gotten into the habit of caIIing RacheI...
“妈咪”,只要是艾玛在场
...''Mommy'' when we're around Emma.
我现在发现她并不在
Which I now reaIize we are not.
我希望如果她听久了 这将成为她第一句会说的话
I'm hoping that if she hears it enough, it'II be her first word.
如果我们真的要这样做 你也应该叫我“爹地”才对
AIthough if we're gonna do that, we shouId probabIy caII me ''Daddy'' too.
我喜欢,爹地
I Iike that, Daddy.
我只是在说瑞秋
I was just taIking about RacheI.
爹地生气了吗?
Is Daddy getting angry?
爹地要打我吗?
Is Daddy gonna spank me?
嗯,要看情况
WeII, that depends.
你是不是坏…? 不,我演不下去了
Have you been a bad--? No, I can't.
哈?哈?嘿,查理 还有其他人知道吗?
HeIIo? HeIIo? Hey, CharIie. Did anybody eIse hear?
什么?苏珊拿到了?怎么会呢?
What? Susan got it? How?
喔,天啊,早知道我也跟他上床!
Oh, man, I wouId've sIept with him!
好了,拜
AII right, bye.
老兄,我很抱歉 但是,还有一个名额不是吗?
Dude, I'm sorry. But hey, there's one spot Ieft, right?
-查理会得到的 -嘿,别那样说
-WeII, CharIie's gonna get that. -Hey, don't say that.
你也有机会得到那工作的
You've got just as good a chance of getting that job.
他是老板的貌子
He is the boss' son.
-好了,乐透! -是啊!
-Come on, Iottery! -Yeah!
-再大概二十分钟就开奖了 -好了,我们来吧
-It starts in, Iike, 20 minutes. -Okay, here we go.
我们需要快点分配这些彩券来对奖
We need to sort through the tickets quickIy to see if we've won.
有人有什么主意要怎么安排吗?
So does anybody have any ideas how to organize this?
好的,看看这样如何
Okay, how about this:
我们分成六组各四十张
We divide them into six groups of 40.
剩下的十张就由先对完的人来对
The remaining 1 0 can be read by whoever finishes first.
-我还有一个主意 -很抱歉,提议时间已经过了
-I have another idea. -I'm sorry, idea time is over.
-所有的彩券都在碗里了吗? -是的
-WeII, are aII the tickets in the bowI? -Yeah.
-那床头柜上面的那些呢? -那边没有彩券
-What about the ones on the nightstand? -There are no tickets there.
是的,那边有 我几分钟前才看到
Yes, there are. I just saw them a few minutes ago.
不对,没有,你看错了
No, you didn't. You must be mistaken.
-床头柜上有二十张彩券 -钱德,注意我的语气
-There are 20 tickets on the nightstand. -ChandIer, sense the tone.
喔,喔,喔,瞧瞧妈咪找到了什么
WeII, weII, weII. Look what Mommy found.
好啦,我帮自己跟钱德多买了二十张
Okay, fine. I bought 20 extra tickets for me and ChandIer.
算命的还说我会被朋友给背叛
The psychic aIso said that I wouId be betrayed.
我不敢相信,我以为我们是一起的
I can't beIieve this. I thought we were aII in this together.
-嘿,你五分钟前才加入的! -是三分钟!
-Hey, you just got in five minutes ago! -Three minutes ago!
我不知道那有什么重要的
I don't know why that's important.
我一直都跟你在一起 你是什么时候买的?
I was with you the whoIe time. When did you even get those?
当你在看未拆封的色情书刊的时候
When you were reading the dirty magazines without taking off the pIastic.
我再分给你看
I'II show you how.
好了,摩妮卡 假设你的彩券中奖了怎么办?
Okay. WeII, Monica, suppose one of your speciaI tickets wins?
你觉得中了彩券 失去了朋友又怎样?
How are you gonna feeI when you win and Iose your friends?
拜,如果我中奖了 你们才不会离开我
PIease. If I win the Iottery, you guys are not gonna Ieave me.
有人上星期给我一堆松饼 害我整整三天都被你们骚扰!
Someone gave me muffins Iast week, and I couIdn't get rid of you for three days!
钱德,你可以告诉她这是不对的吗?
ChandIer, wouId you just teII her what she did was wrong?
她说的对,你不应该 帮我们两个另买彩券
She's right. You shouIdn't have bought tickets just for us.
让我说完
Let me finish.
然而,看起来我好像得不到这份工作了
However, it doesn't Iook Iike I'm gonna get this job...
所以我不能太有原则 去你们的!彩券是我们的!
...so I can't afford to have principIes. So screw you! The tickets are ours!
这才是我嫁的好男人
There's the man I married.
好了,相信我,如果你们中奖了
AII right. BeIieve me, if you win the Iottery...
你们就跟我们不是朋友了
...it's the Iast you're gonna hear from us.
无所谓,不要当我的朋友就算了 我会买新朋友的
Fine. Don't be my friends. I'II buy new friends.
是的,我还会付钱让他们动整形手术 让他们看起来跟你们一模一样!
Yeah, and then I'II pay for their pIastic surgery so they Iook just Iike you!
你知道吗?我要拿回我的份
You know what? I want my share of the tickets.
我也要拿回我的彩券! 而且我要买下尼克队!
I want my tickets too! And I'm buying the Knicks!
还有葛拉芙!
And Steffi Graf!
太好了,那我也要拿回我的! 而且如果我中奖…
CooI. Then I want mine too! And if I win...
我要拿全部的钱去买低利公债!
...I'm gonna put it aII into a very Iow-yieId bond!
不行,我们必须要 把全部的彩券集合在一起
No. You guys, we gotta keep aII the tickets together.
不,我们应该分一分
No. No, we shouId divide them up...
而且我应该多分点 因为是开我的车买的!
...and I shouId get extra because we used my car!
嘿!嘿!如果有人可以多拿一些 那个人应该是我!
Hey! Hey! If anybody gets extra tickets, it shouId be me!
-这整件事都是我想出来的! -是啊,谢谢你发明乐透!
-This whoIe thing was my idea! -Yeah. Thanks for inventing the Iottery!
把彩券给我,我来分!
Just give them to me, and I'II spIit them up!
嘿,嘿!
Hey, hey!
天啊,我再也受不了了! 我来结束这一切!
God, I can't take it anymore! I'm putting an end to this!
-如果她跳楼了,她的彩券就是我的! -等等,不!嘿!
-Okay, if she jumps, I get her tickets! -Wait, no, no! Hey!
如果我们不要一起合资 那我们就什么都不要
If we're not doing this together, we're not doing it at aII.
-跟你们的彩券说再见吧 -不!不!不!
-Say goodbye to your tickets. -No! No! No!
不要再靠近过来了!
Do not come any cIoser!
我可以再靠近一点点吗? 我的宝贝被压到了
Can I come a IittIe bit cIoser? VaIuabIe things are getting squished.
现在,什么比较重要? 朋友还是钱?
Now, what's more important, your friends or money?
-朋友! -钱!
-Friends! -Money!
朋友
Friends.
嘿,摩妮卡,那你其它的彩券呢?
Hey, Monica, what about your extra tickets?
全都在里面了
They're aII in there.
-还有我内衣藏的这五张 -摩妮卡!
-Even these five that I hid in my bra. -Monica!
好的,很好,你们都吓坏了
Okay. Good. You guys were so scared.
我根本不可能会丢掉这些…
There is no way I was gonna dump this--
天啊!不!
God! No!
我想我把你的碗摔破了
I think I broke your bowI.
快、快、快!
Go! Go! Go!
到街上去找彩券 真是美好的夜晚啊
What a beautifuI night to be running around the street, Iooking for tickets.
而且被风一吹就更有趣了
And the wind sure made it fun.
-菲比,有一半不见了 -那又如何呢?
-Phoebe, we Iost haIf of them. -So what?
摩妮卡,我们还是会中奖的
Monica, we have the winning ticket.
算命师说我会中奖的,记得吗?
My psychic said I was gonna win, remember?
奇怪的是 算命师并没有算到可怕的鸽子
Weird your psychic didn't mention anything about the scary pigeon.
事实上她是有说过 我会那样死去
As a matter of fact, she said that's how I'm going to die.
所以,原谅我有点被吓到
So excuse me for being a IittIe skittish.
有两通留言,可能是工作的消息
There's two messages. This couId be from work.
-喔,放来听听 -好了,来了
-Oh, pIay them. -Okay. Here we go.
哈,我是阳台上的鸽子 打电话过来道歉的
Hello. This is the pigeon from the balcony calling to apologize.
我不应该把彩券 从那个漂亮小姐手中弄翻
I shouldn't have knocked the tickets out of the pretty lady's hand.
这全是我的错,不关她的事,拜
It was all my fault. Not hers. Bye.
嗯,我敢说要这样道歉 一定很难
WeII, I bet that was very hard for him to do.
嘿,钱德,我是查理
Hey, Chandler, it's Charlie.
就是这个了
This is it.
听着,结果是我拿到最后的名额
Listen, it turns out I got the last spot.
我很抱歉,老兄 很高兴跟你共事过
I'm really sorry, man. It was a lot of fun working with you.
再打电话给我吧
Give me a call if you want.
天啊,我很难过,亲爱的
Gosh, I'm so sorry, honey.
真替你难过,钱德
Sorry, ChandIer.
这真是不公平,这就像那次 他们升珊卓,而不是我一样
It is so unfair. It's Iike that time they promoted Saundra over me at work.
她跟洛夫罗伦有亲戚关系吗?
Was she reIated to RaIph Lauren?
没有,只是她工作能力比我强太多了
No, she was just much better at her job than me.
你们大家,快要开奖了
You guys, the drawing's about to start.
我们应该打电话给我妈 跟艾玛说晚安
We shouId caII my mom's and say good night to Emma...
-赶在她睡着以前 -好主意
-...before she goes down. -Good idea.
亲爱的,面对这件事你真的很坚强
Honey, you're being reaIIy strong about this.
我知道你很想要这份工作
I know how badIy you wanted that job.
是啊,你知道的 我真的以为这是该给我的
Yeah, you know, I reaIIy thought I deserved it.
让我们来中乐透吧 我们还有一百三十个机会不是吗?
But Iet's go win the Iottery. I mean, we stiII have a 1 30 chances to win, right?
一百三十一个
Hundred and thirty-one.
是的,晚安甜心,我爱你
Yeah, good night, sweetheart. I Iove you.
还有记住,你是爹地的小女孩
And remember, you're Daddy's IittIe girI.
菲比完全毁了“爹地”
Phoebe's totaIIy ruined that for me.
嗨,妈,让艾玛听
Hi, Mom. Put her back on.
瑞秋,他们在开奖了!
Rach, they're announcing the numbers!
我的天啊,我可以感到自己在改变了
My God, I can aIready feeI myseIf changing.
这里是正式超级大乐透中奖号码 我们有五十三
Here are your official Powerball numbers. We have 53.
-我有 -我们也有一个!
-I've got that. -We have one too!
我们快中奖了!
We are on the road, peopIe!
快点!
Come on!
妈,拜,我知道你喜欢你的新嘴唇 但是我不太懂你在说什么
Mom, pIease, I know you Iove your new Iips, but I can bareIy understand you.
你可以让我跟我女貌道晚安吗?
WouId you pIease just Iet me say good night to my daughter?
然后接下来的号码是七
And here we go. The Powerball is seven.
好了,你们快对号码! 让我发财吧!
AII right, check your numbers! Make me rich.
你们大家,你们不会相信这个的
You guys, you're not gonna beIieve this.
我刚刚在跟艾玛说晚安的时候 她说了第一句话
I was just saying good night to Emma, and she said her first words.
-什么? -那她说了什么呢?
-What? -WeII, what did she say?
她说了“葛利巴”!
She said, ''GIeba'' !
让我发财吧!
Make me rich!
-是不是很惊人呢? -是啊,真是太棒了
-Isn't that amazing? -Oh, yeah. No, no, no, that's great.
为什么你没有很兴奋呢?
Why aren't you more excited?
瑞秋,葛利巴不算一句话
Rach, gIeba is not a word.
-它当然算 -好吧,那它是什么意思呢?
-WeII, of course it is. -Okay. What does it mean?
嗯,我又不认识所有的字词
WeII, I don't know aII the words.
我只是很高兴我没有错过 我女貌说第一句话
You know, I'm just gIad I didn't miss my daughter's first word.
-你就是错过了!葛利巴算! -好的,那用它造句
-Yes you did! GIeba is a word! -Okay. Use it in a sentence.
好的,艾玛刚刚说了“葛利巴”
Okay. Emma just said, ''GIeba.''
-那不算说话 -好的,我来查字典
-It's not a word. -Okay, fine. I'm gonna Iook it up.
好的,太好了
Okay, great.
顺便查一下 有天她也说了另外一句…
WhiIe you're at it, she said another word the other day.
你何不也查查看这个:
Why don't you Iook up:
好了,葛利巴,葛利巴,葛利巴!
AII right. Okay. Okay. GIeba. GIeba. GIeba. GIeba!
找到了!“含孢子的丰厚菌种”
Here it is! ''The fIeshy, spore-bearing inner mass of a certain fungi.''
她会成为科学家的
She's gonna be a scientist.
-该死的,有人有对到吗? -没有
-Damn it. Anybody got anything? -No.
我还在对我的
I'm stiII Iooking through mine.
再对一次,没有
Just doubIe-checking. No.
没有,没有
No. No.
没有!
No!
哈?等一下
HeIIo? HoId on.
是你老板
It's your boss.
“很抱歉没用你”的电话来了
The ''I'm sorry I rejected you'' phone caII.
我还真不习惯男生打这种电话来
I'm not used to getting these from guys.
-嘿,史提夫 -钱德,嗨
-Hey, Steve. -ChandIer, hi.
我想你已经听说我们三个名额都满了
I'm sure you've heard we fiIIed the three positions.
我们觉得以你的成熟度及经验
We feIt that with your maturity and experience...
你不会想要当助理的
...you wouIdn't be happy being someone's assistant.
我爱死当助理了,接听电话…
I'd Iove to be somebody's assistant. Answering phones...
倒咖啡,我就是为那些工作而活的
...getting coffee, I Iive for that stuff.
而且我并没有很成熟 放屁、咪咪、屁蛋!
And I'm not too mature. Farts, boobies, butt cracks!
钱德,你是全部的人里面最优秀的
ChandIer, you were the strongest person in the program.
我们要聘请你当初级广告文案
We're offering you the position of junior copywriter.
我?那个刚刚才说“屁蛋”的人?
Me? That guy who just said, ''butt cracks''?
是的,没错
Yes, that's right.
我们很期望你能带给这份工作…
We're excited about the IeveI of sophistication...
一定程度的深度
...you'II be bringing to the job.
好的,谢谢,你不会失望的 明天见
Okay. WeII, thanks, you won't regret it. I'II see you tomorrow.
怎样?
What?
对,我要当初级广告文案了
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be a junior copywriter.
恭喜了!亲爱的,我真以你为荣
CongratuIations! Oh, sweetie, I'm so proud of you.
谢谢,这表示我今晚可以被爱爱吗?
Thanks. Does that mean I get the good Ioving tonight?
当然,不看电视或什么其它的
You bet. No TV or anything.
-嘿,恭喜你找到工作了 -谢了,老兄
-Hey, that is so great about the job. -Thanks, man.
我其实也有帮到忙
I'd Iike to think I had something to do with it.
-真的吗?怎么说? -刚刚在玩幸福骨头的时候…
-ReaIIy? Why? -WeII, before with the wishbone.
我没有许愿我们中乐透 我许的愿是你找到工作
I didn't wish we wouId win the Iottery. I wished you'd get the job.
喔,是吗?
Oh, yeah?
听着,别告诉摩妮卡 她会把你的心脏挖出来的
Listen, don't teII Monica. She'II rip your heart right out.
你们知道吗?我一直有一点点感觉
WeII, you know what? There was a IittIe part of me...
觉得我们好像真的会中奖
...that reaIIy thought we were gonna win.
我也是,都是为了我的恐龙与 女飞行员主题公园
Me too. So much for my dinosaur/ AmeIia Earhart theme park.
You guys? What was the PowerbaII number again?
-七 -我们中奖了
-Seven. -We won.
-什么? -我们中奖了!
-What? -We won!
-让我看,让我看 -别撕掉了
-Let me see! Let me see! -Don't tear it!
菲比,你其它五个号码都不对!
Phoebe, you don't have any of the first five numbers!
我知道,但是我们中了特别号 我们中了三块钱!
I know that, but Iook, we got the PowerbaII number. We won $3!
哇,你觉得我们应该分二十年提领 还是一次领光呢?
Wow, you think we shouId get that over 20 years or go for the big payout?
我不管,我从来就没有 中过任何东西,我真不敢相信!
I don't care. I've never won anything before. I can't beIieve this!
菲比,你要怎么运用这三块钱呢?
So, Pheebs, what are you gonna do with your $3?
又不是全都是我的 我们每个人都有五十分
WeII, it's not aII mine. We aII get 50 cents.
你知道吗?我的份给你
You know what? You can have mine.
-我的也是 -我的也是
-Me too. -Me too.
我的也是
Me too.
好吧,既然大家都要给你
WeII, I guess if everybody eIse is.
(中央咖啡厅)
嘿,我刚刚打电话给乐透公司
Hey, guys. So I just caIIed the PowerbaII hot Iine.
-你们敢相信吗?没有人中奖耶 -我希望不是那样
-Can you beIieve it? Nobody won. -I beg to differ.
或许没有人中头奖 但是稍早有个人在这里…
Maybe nobody won the jackpot, but there was this guy in here earIier...
在外面捡到一张彩券 中了一万块钱
...and he found a ticket on the street right outside and won $ 1 0,000.
不要再责怪漂亮小姐了
Again, don't bIame the pretty Iady.
那不是她的错,是鸽子我的错
It was not her fauIt. It was me, the pigeon.
真的,不要再瞪她了
SeriousIy, stop staring at her.